

LINIT VACHALI

056 1212407 , +91 9562450908 Linitlintu@gmail .com

Professional Summary:

With diverse experience in System Administrator for almost 2.9 year, I am currently looking for a career growth with a major corporate, who uses the latest technologies in Networking Domain and to work with commitment and dedication, which will enhance my project/people management and technical skills and realize my potential.

 Excellent Organizational and communication skills and would like to seek good position in a dynamic and challenging professional environment.

Professional Experience:

MICROHARD SERVICES Pvt Ltd, Bangalore

Designation: System Administrator Period: MAY 2016 – MARCH 2019

Payroll Company: Microhard services Pvt Ltd

Client Company: 1. SURVEY OF INDIA (MAY 2016- NOV 2017)

2. CHRIST UNIVERSITY (DEC 2017 –MARCH 2019)

Job Responsibilities:

- Handled maintenance of Desktops and laptops with Windows Support along with monitoring system performance.
- Diagnose hardware and software problems, and replace defective components
- Assemble and disassemble the desktops computers
- · Configure and troubleshoots the network printer, local printer and scanner
- Run and configure network cables, troubleshoot connectivity issues, create users and configure other related issues.
- · Configuration and Troubleshooting of Switches, Wi-Fi devices.
- · Configuring and Monitoring of ADS, DNS, DHCP
- · Adding from workgroup to domain system, User ID creation and giving admin Permission
- Software and Hardware Installation.
- Troubleshooting Windows, Hardware and Network related issues.

Skill Summary:

- Windows server and client OS installation
- Hardware and Network related issues
- Troubleshooting Windows
- Software Installation.
- Hardware Installation
- troubleshoots the network printer, local printer and scanner
- Diagnose hardware
- LAN
- Troubleshooting

Educational Profile:

2015 Bachelor of Science (BSc): ELECTRONICS Institution: College of Applied Science Kuthuparamba

University: Kannur University

Course completed

2011 HSE (Class XI and Class XII):

Institution: Govt. Vocational Higher Secondary School, Chirakkara

Board: Board of Public Examination, Kerala

Percentage Scored: 65%

2010 SSLC (Class X):

Institution: Kuthuparamba High School, Thokkilangadi

Board: Board of Public Examination, Kerala

Percentage Scored: 67%

Additional Qualification:

Completed Jetking Certified Network Administrator (JCNA) course from Jetking Jayanagar Learning Centre, Bengaluru from June 2016

Project:

STUDENT COLLEGE ALERT SYSTEM BY USING RFID&GSM

Personal Information:

Date of Birth : 01-FEB-1993

Address : KALLYDAN VEEDU,

KUTHUPARAMBA Mangattidom P.O

Kannur 670643 Kerala • Male

Sex : Male

Father Name : N Balakrishnan

Nationality : Indian

Languages : English, Malayalam, tamil

Visa Status : VISIT VISA

Declaration:

I hereby declare that the information furnished above is true to the best of my knowledge and belief.

UAE. Dubai. LINIT VACHALI